<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Sarath Sadasivan Pillai</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Sarath Sadasivan Pillai</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:10:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sarathsp.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gojson : A Simple JSON Parser</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/gojson/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:10:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarathsp.com/projects/gojson/</guid><description>GoJSON is a command line utility to handle JSON serialised data. You can find the code here
What it does Pretty print JSON Retrieve nested objects Validate JSON Aggregate functions Installing Go Dev version
$ go get -u github.com/sarathsp06/gojson Binray Release
download and use the binary as such for your platform
Tip: In unix move the binary to PATH
Key Syntax Key is a set of .</description></item><item><title>Sublime Php Selective Format</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/sublime-php-selective-format/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 09:07:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarathsp.com/projects/sublime-php-selective-format/</guid><description>A sublime plugin to format php code snippets without disturbing the other parts of the file There are a lot of legacy PHP programs that people maintain actively, some of them does not follow proper coding standards and thus it limits the developer from adhering to standards for newer code also. The tooling available for PHP code fixing are all to fix the entire file and since doing that would make the diff much bigger people can&amp;rsquo;t use it</description></item><item><title>Gologger</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/gologger/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 08:56:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarathsp.com/projects/gologger/</guid><description>Logger library for the gophers An opinionated logging library for golang. Gologger writes logs as json in the following format
{ &amp;quot;time&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;2016-11-10T16:11:46.59Z&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;process_name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;sample_logger&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;host_name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;sarath.local&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;process_id&amp;quot;:29422, &amp;quot;level&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;ERROR&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;file_name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;/home/sarath/go/src/github.com/sarathsp06/gologger/sample/main.go&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;line_num&amp;quot;:13, &amp;quot;log_msg&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;error happened&amp;quot; } That much info will be how following will be written
logger.Error(&amp;quot;error happened&amp;quot;) Installing / Getting started Just like any other go library
go get github.com/sarathsp06/gologger But if one needs to get a particular version then use</description></item><item><title>Exotel Py</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/exotel-py/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:09:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarathsp.com/projects/exotel-py/</guid><description>Python module for Exotel&amp;rsquo;s call and sms APIs. exotel-py
Installation pip install exotel Usage Initialize from exotel import Exotel client = Exotel(sid,token) make call to connect a number to another client.call_number(&#39;from_number&#39;,&#39;exophone&#39;,&#39;to_number&#39;) make call to connect a number to a flow client.call_flow(&#39;from_number&#39;,&#39;exophone&#39;,&#39;flow_id&#39;) send an sms client.sms(&#39;from_number&#39;,to_number&#39;,&amp;quot;sms_body&amp;quot;) get details of an sms client.sms_details(&#39;sms_sid&#39;) get details of a call client.</description></item><item><title>Python 2factor Client</title><link>https://sarathsp.com/projects/python-2factor-client/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 01:09:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarathsp.com/projects/python-2factor-client/</guid><description>Two-factor authentication (also known as 2FA) is a type (subset) of multi-factor authentication. It is a method of confirming a user&amp;rsquo;s claimed identity by utilizing a combination of two different factors:
something they know, something they have, or something they are. py2factor app Two Factor authentication app for desktop (Linux). The app can be used along with other two factor applications like authy ,google authenticator etc. Unlike the mobile two factor authenticators ,this app requires the user to read the QR given for two factor using mobile and pass the data read from that as input to the application</description></item></channel></rss>